

Full Stack Web Developer

### Profile

Passionate full stack web developer with nearly 4 years of junior position experience in various aspects of development.

When I'm not in school or on a adventure, I spend my time developing web applications or websites using React, Next, or Gatsby. Very rarely, you can spot me automating my daily tasks using Python, or constructing Arduino/RPi projects.

## Employment History

Junior frontend web developer at Webops, Brno

October 2021 — Present

Developing and deploying custom made frontend websites using React.js or Next.js, occasionally Wordpress templates and themes for ecommerce sites.

#### **Fullstack Freelancer**

April 2021 — Present

Developed full stack web portfolio solution including web page (web gallery) using vanilla JavaScript and Webpack as well as it's custom content management system using React.js and Firebase for an amateur photographer.

This project is also my Final Year project, so for school purposes I built complete CI/CD pipeline which deploys latest changes in the code base to my virtual private server.

### Education

Střední průmyslová škola, Obchodní akademie a jazyková škola, Frýdek-Místek

September 2018 — Present

My current high school I attend and supposed to graduate in May 2022.

# Internships

Linux server administrator at TietoEvry, Ostrava

May 2021 — January 2022

### Courses

European Computer Driving Licence, ECDL Czech Republic

March 2020 — Present

IT Essentials, Cisco

November 2019 — Present

#### **Details**

+420 774 460 131 jiri.vala11@gmail.com

#### Links

Github Profile LinkedIn Profile

### **Skills And Technologies**

JavaScript

Typescript

React.js

Git

Linux

Gatsby.js

Next.js

Node.js

CI/CD

Firebase (Hosting, Databases)

Python

SASS/SCSS

C#

C++ basics (Arduino projects)

OOP

#### Languages

Czech

**English**